In this video we are going to use what we have learned so far about self-type to
在这段视频中，我们将使用我们目前所学到的关于自我类型的知识来
incorporate the self-type into the type checking rules for Cool. First let's
将自类型合并到Cool的类型检查规则中。首先让我们
remind ourselves what the type checking rules for Cool actually prove. So the
提醒我们Cool的类型检查规则实际上证明了什么。因此，
sentences in the type logic look like this, and they prove things are the form
类型逻辑中的句子看起来是这样的，它们证明了事物就是
that some expression has some type, and they do that under the assumption that
一些表达式有某种类型，他们这样做是在假设
object identifiers have some types given by O, methods have signatures given by M,
对象标识符有一些由O给出的类型，方法有由M给出的签名，
and the enclosing class, the current class in which E sits, in, in which we are doing
而封闭的类，也就是E所在的当前类，也就是我们正在做的
our type checking, is class C. And the whole reason for this additional piece
我们的类型检查是C类，而这个附加部分的全部原因是
here we haven't actually discussed this before why we needed this C. It is because
在这里，我们实际上没有讨论过为什么我们需要这个C。这是因为
self-types meaning depends on the enclosing class. So if you recall we.
自我类型的意义取决于所包围的班级。所以如果你还记得我们。
Introduce this notation, self type sub C to record and what class a particular
介绍这个符号，自己类型子C来记录，以及一个特定的类是什么
occurrence of self-type sits. And this C in the environment is exactly that
自体式坐姿的发生。环境中的这个C就是
subscript, it is tracking what class we are in. So when we see occurrences, an
下标，它在跟踪我们所在的班级。所以当我们看到事件发生时，一个
occurrence of self-type we know what kind of self-type. We're talking about so now
自我类型的发生我们知道什么样的自我类型。我们现在谈论的是
I'm ready to actually give the type rules that use self-type. And for the most part,
我已经准备好实际给出使用self类型的类型规则。在很大程度上，
this is really easy, because the rules just remain the same. That is, they look
这真的很容易，因为规则只是保持不变。也就是说，他们看起来
the same, but they're actually a little bit different, because they use the new
相同，但实际上有一点不同，因为它们使用新的
sub typing and least upper bound operations that we defined before. So for
前面定义的子类型和最小上界操作。所以对于
example, here is the rule for assignment, and this looks identical to the rule for
例如，下面是赋值规则，它看起来与
assignment that we discussed several videos ago. But notice that this use of
我们在几个视频之前讨论过的作业。但请注意，这种使用
sub-typing here is now the extended definition of sub-typing to incorporate
这里的子类型现在是子类型的扩展定义，
self-type. So now this rule works with self-type as well as with the normal class
自我类型。现在这条规则既适用于Self类型，也适用于Normal类
names. Now there are some rules that have change in the presents of self-type. And
名字。现在有一些规则在自我类型的呈现上有了变化。和
in particular the dispatch rules need to be updated. So here is the old rule for
具体地说，需要更新派单规则。所以这是一个古老的规则
dynamic dispatch. And this rule, this part of the rule, actually doesn't change. It
动态调度。这条规则，规则的这一部分，实际上是不变的。它
stays the same. But, I just wanna point out the essential restriction in this
保持不变。但是，我只想指出这一点的本质限制
rule, is that the return type of the method could not be self-type. And that's
规则是该方法的返回类型不能为自类型。那就是
actually the place where self-type buys us something. So the whole purpose of having
实际上，自我型给我们买东西的地方。所以我们要做的就是
self-type is to have methods who's return type is self-type. Because that's were we
Self类型是指具有返回类型为Self类型的方法。因为那就是我们
actually get the extra expressive power. And know we have to consider the case, now
实际上获得了额外的表现力。并且知道我们现在必须考虑这个案子
that we have self typing we done all this work, what if the methods return type is
我们有自己的类型，我们完成了所有这些工作，如果方法返回的类型是
self type. How are we going to type check that? Well here's the rule. So as usual,
自我类型。我们要怎么打字检查一下？嗯，规则是这样的。所以像往常一样，
we type check the. The expression that we're dispatching to that's E zero and all
我们键入check。我们要分派给它的表达式是E0和All
of the argument and we just get their type. And their just type checked in the
而我们只是得到了他们的类型。并且他们刚刚的类型签入了
same environmental as the entire expression. And now just like before we
与整个表达式的环境相同。现在，就像以前一样，我们
look up in class T0 the type of E0, the method F and we get its signature. Okay.
在类T0中查找E0的类型，方法F，我们就得到了它的签名。好吧。
And then we have to check that the arguments conform. That every actual
然后我们必须检查论点是否一致。每一个实际的
argument, E1 through En, has a type that's compatible with the corresponding formal
参数e1到en的类型与相应的形式
parameter in the method signature. And if all of that works out, then we can say
方法签名中的参数。如果所有这些都成功了，那么我们可以说
that this dispatch is going to have type, oh look, T0. So where did that come from?
这个调度的类型是，哦，看，T0。那这是从哪里来的呢？
Well, the return type is self-type. And so the result of this entire dispatch is
嗯，返回类型是Self类型。所以整个调度的结果是
going to be the type of whatever e zero was. E zero is the self-parameter.
将会是类似于eZero的类型。E零是自参数。
Whatever type we got for e zero, that is a sound static type for the result of the
不管我们得到的是什么类型的eZero，这都是一个声音静电类型，它的结果是
entire expression. So we simply use the type of e zero as the type of the entire,
整个表达式。所以我们简单地使用e0的类型作为整体的类型，
static, the entire dynamic dispatch. Now recall the full parameters of a function
静电，整个动态调度。现在回想一下函数的完整参数
cannot have type self type, but the actual arguments can have type self type, and the
不能具有类型Self类型，但实际参数可以具有类型Self类型，并且
extended sub typing relationship will handle that case just fine. One
扩展子类型关系将很好地处理这种情况。一
interesting detail is that the dispatch expression itself could have a type,
有趣的细节是调度表达式本身可以有一个类型，
self-type. And, so what do I mean by that, well, let's think about E zero.
自我类型。那么，我这么说是什么意思，让我们考虑一下E0。
Dispatching to method F, and then what happens if E zero has type self type? What
调度到方法F，然后如果E0具有类型Self类型，会发生什么情况？什么
if we can prove that E zero has type self type. And the problem here is that we need
如果我们能证明E0有自型。这里的问题是我们需要
to lo okay up, in the, in the M environment, in the method environment, in
往上看，在M环境中，在方法环境中，在
some class. The definition of or the signature of method F/, we have to get
一些阶级。方法F/的定义或签名，我们必须得到
back that type signature so we can do the rest of that type checking. And if E0 has
返回该类型签名，以便我们可以进行该类型检查的睡觉。如果E0有
type soft type normally we use the type of E0 to do that, to do that look up. What
通常我们使用E0的类型来做这件事，为了做那个查找。什么
type do we use here? Well, if this whole thing is occurring in class C. If we have,
我们在这里使用的类型是什么？如果整件事都发生在C班如果我们有，
if we're type checking in class C. >> You just put the line there. >> And it's safe
如果我们在类C中进行类型检查，您只需将行放在那里即可。>>而且很安全
and this is a soft type sub c and as always it's safe to replace soft type sub
这是软类型SUB c，和往常一样，替换软类型SUB是安全的
c by c. So, we'll just use the class c there. The correct class that we are type
乘以，所以我们在那里只使用类。我们键入的正确类
checking in to look up the method name test. We have to make similar changes to
签入以查找方法名测试。我们必须做出类似的改变
the rules for static dispatch. So, here is the original rule for the static dispatch
静电派单的规则。因此，这是静电派遣的原始规则
and... And again, this part of the rule will not change. Uh... This... This
而且..。再说一次，规则的这一部分不会改变。呃..。这个。这
handles the case, where the return type of the method is not the self-type. But if
处理方法的返回类型不是Self类型的情况。但是如果
the return type of the method is self-typed, then the rule looks a little
该方法的返回类型是自类型的，那么规则看起来有点
bit different. So, we, once again we type check, the, expression that we're
有点不一样。所以，我们，我们再一次键入check，我们正在
dispatching to and all the arguments in the same environment as that of the entire
将所有参数调度到与整个
expression. We have to check that the class we're dispatching to, the type t
表达式。我们必须检查我们要调度到的类、类型t
zero, is a sub type of the class, named in the static dispatch. We have to look up
零，是类的子类型，在静电调度中命名。我们得往上看
the method. It has to exist in that class that we're statically dispatching to. So
该方法。它必须存在于我们静态调度到的那个类中。所以
we have to look up in class T, the method F and get its signature. And then we have
我们必须在类T中查找方法F，并获得它的签名。然后我们就有了
to check that the actual arguments conform to the formal parameters of their types.
检查实际参数是否与其类型的形参一致。
If the types of the arguments match the types, the declared types of the formal
如果参数的类型与类型匹配，则正式
parameters. And then, the only thing that's kind of curious about this rule, is
参数。然后，这条规则唯一让人好奇的是
that the result type here is, again, T zero. And, why is that right? It could
这里的结果类型也是T0。那么，为什么会这样呢？它可能会
have been a, a T. It could have been the type to which we statically dispatched.
已经是一个，一个T。它可能是我们静态调度到的那种类型。
And it's not because self-type is the type of the self-parameter. And even though
这并不是因为自我类型是自我参数的类型。即使是这样
we're dispatching to a method in class T , the self-parameter still has type T0. And
我们正在调度到类T中的一个方法，自参数的类型仍然是T0。和
recall that T0 is a subtype of T. So we use the static dispatch to reach a method
回想一下，T0是T的子类型，因此我们使用静电调度来到达一个方法
definition that's hidden potentially by overwrite, overwritten methods, in the
定义可能被重写、重写的方法隐藏在
subclasses. But that doesn't change the type of the self-parameter. The
子类。但这不会改变自参数的类型。这个
self-parameter still has type T0 even though we're running a method. Of the, in
即使我们正在运行一个方法，自参数仍然具有类型T0。的，在
a superclass of G,0. There two new rules for self- type. One involves the
G的一个超类，0。关于自我类型有两条新规则。一个涉及到
self-object. So, the self-object has type self-type sub-C. And notice this is one of
自我客体。因此，自我对象的类型为自身类型子C。请注意，这是其中一个
those places where we need to know the enclosing class. So, we know what kind of
那些我们需要知道其所属班级的地方。所以我们知道是什么样的
self-type we're referring to. And similarly there's a rule for allocating
我们指的是自我类型。类似地，也有一条分配规则
something of type self-type. So, a, the expression new self-type also produces
自我类型的东西。所以，第一，表达新的自我类型也会产生
something of type self-type sub-C.
自体型的东西，分C型的。